[Music]
Power cords ring out as I sit at my
desk.
Riffing the day dreams running through
my head.
Scrolling the endless
feed for some delight.
Online I'm loud. Offline I stay out of
sight.
[Music]
Boot of my day.
I'm ready to post. Snap a new P. Filter
it the most.
Followers blind, but I'm stuck in my
room. IRL is out of tune.
Scream name is B.
My avatar's cool. Like by a crowd I
never met at school.
DMs are fire.
Replies coming fast. But real
conversations never last.
I'm online.
That's what my boss says.
I
can't look in the eye.
I'm a legend
be on my Wi-Fi
[Music]
photo.
I'm living a me scroll and pretend I
know what I mean.
Laughing emoji
to cover the pain. I'll find my jokes.
Don't let the same
behind the screen of everything I want
to be. But face to face I always
[Music]
got the perfect
inside.
[Music]